http://www.concordiatechnology.org/privacy-statement?hsLang=en

Your Privacy Is Our Priority
Concordia Technology Solutions is a division of Concordia Publishing House, the publishing arm of The Lutheran Church–Missouri Synod.
Privacy Notice
Privacy: Concordia Publishing House respects and wants to protect the privacy of our users. We do not collect your name or email address, unless you provide it on a registration form, order form, survey form, or send us an email.  Our site's forms may ask or require you to give us contact information (like your email address), financial information (like your account or credit card numbers), and demographic information (like your zip code). We use this information to provide information, products, or services that you request. For example, financial information is used to bill you for products and services that you order. Any information collected is for internal use and is not made available to any outside company or organization except in the performance of our responsibilities to you as our customer (i.e. credit card numbers are used to process transactions with third party financial institutions). We share customer information only with organizations that are acting on our behalf to conduct specific activities, such as our auditors. We do not sell the names and addresses of our customers.
Use and Collection of Information: We collect aggregate data (for example how many times a certain page is visited). We may also record search terms used to refine our search engine.  We only collect personally identifiable information (like your name) when you create an account with us, submit a form, place an order, or contact us and provide this information.
Remarketing: The Concordia Publishing House websites may use Google AdWords, Facebook, or Twitter to match you with specific marketing information matched to the activities you perform on the websites.  Google, Facebook, Twitter, and other third party vendors use cookies to serve ads based on past visits to the website. You may opt out of third party’s use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising initiative opt-out page (http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp), or by opting out from each of the following:
Google: http://www.google.com/settings/ads
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads
Twitter: https://twitter.com/settings/security
Ownership of Feedback: Concordia Publishing House welcomes your comments and feedback regarding this site. All information and materials submitted to Concordia Publishing House through this site or otherwise, such as any comments, feedback, ideas, questions, designs, data or the like, but not content (collectively, "Feedback"), will be considered NON-CONFIDENTIAL and NON-PROPRIETARY with regard to you, but Concordia Publishing House reserves the right to treat any such Feedback as the confidential information of Concordia Publishing House. For this reason, we ask you not to send us any information or materials that you do not wish to assign to us, including, without limitation, any confidential information or any original creative materials such as product ideas, computer code, or original artwork.
By submitting Feedback to Concordia Publishing House through this site, you assign to Concordia Publishing House, free of charge, all worldwide rights, title and interest in all copyrights and other intellectual property rights in the Feedback you submit. Concordia Publishing House will be entitled to use any Feedback you submit to it, and any ideas, concepts, know-how or techniques contained in any such Feedback, for any purpose whatsoever, including but not limited to developing, manufacturing and marketing products and services using such Feedback without restriction and without compensating you in any way.
You are responsible for the information and other content contained in any Feedback you submit to us, including, without limitation, their truthfulness and accuracy.
Contests and Surveys:  Concordia Publishing House occasionally offers contests.  The full rules for our contests are clearly posted during each contest.  The personal information that is gathered through a contest is used only by Concordia Publishing House to verify user identity and to contact winners and/or prize recipients.
Concordia Publishing House may, from time to time, invite you to participate in online surveys.  The information requested in these surveys may include, but is not limited to, your opinions, beliefs, insights, ideas, activities, experience, purchase history, and purchase intent regarding products, events and services.  The information collected by theses surveys is used to research market trends, church trends, ministry growth, congregation and community needs.  Your input will help us to improve customer experience, shape new product development, equip church ministry effectiveness and enhance products for your spiritual growth and experience.
Children's Data: Concordia Publishing House is committed to compliance with applicable laws governing the protection of children's data, such as the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). To that end, Concordia Publishing House will not knowingly seek or encourage anyone under the age of 13 to provide any data through our website. Parents are strongly encouraged to monitor their children's Internet activity, and to assist their children in making positive choices concerning the materials they receive through electronic means. See COPPA statement below..
Disclosure of information practices with regard to children as required by the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA)
Personal information such as the name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, persistent identifier, or combination of various identifying elements, of children under the age of thirteen is not knowingly collected by Concordia Publishing House. If a child chooses to send an e-mail or other electronic request to Concordia Publishing House, we may respond to that e-mail or request. However, the e-mail address of the child will be deleted and no personal information will be collected, stored, or disclosed. If you have questions concerning the information practices of Concordia Publishing House, contact: webservant@CPH.org.
Changes: Concordia Publishing House reserves the right to change this privacy notice at any time by publishing a revised version of this agreement on the site. You are responsible for regularly reviewing this agreement. Continued use of the site following any such changes means you accept and will abide by these changes.
Content Disclaimer
Reminders regarding website content: This website is provided for your information only. All content, software, downloads and functions made available on or accessed through this website are provided “as is, where is” and “as available”. (See "Disclaimer" below.) While Concordia Publishing House does its best to ensure the optimal performance of its website, you agree that you assume all risks concerning the suitability and accuracy of the information. The website may contain technical inaccuracies or typographical errors. Concordia Publishing House assumes no responsibility for and disclaims all liability for any such inaccuracies, errors, or omissions in this website and in other documents referred to within or linked to this website.
Prices, technical specifications, and product offerings are subject to change without notice, at any time.
DISCLAIMER: THIS WEBSITE IS PROVIDED BY CONCORDIA PUBLISHING HOUSE ON AN "AS IS" BASIS. CONCORDIA PUBLISHING HOUSE MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, AS TO THE OPERATION OF THE WEBSITE, OR THE INFORMATION, CONTENT, MATERIALS OR PRODUCTS INCLUDED ON THIS WEBSITE. THIS INCLUDES LOSS OF DATA OR PROFIT ARISING OUT OF THE USE OR THE INABILITY TO USE THE CONTENT OF THIS WEBSITE.  WE DO NOT WARRANT THAT ANY CONTENT OR INFORMATION ACCESSED THROUGH THIS WEBSITE WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR FREE, THAT DEFECTS WILL BE CORRECTED, OR THAT THIS WEBSITE, OR THE SERVER THAT MAKES IT AVAILABLE, IS FREE OF VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS. TO THE FULL EXTENT PERMISSIBLE BY APPLICABLE LAW, CONCORDIA PUBLISHING HOUSE DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO, IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. CONCORDIA PUBLISHING HOUSE WILL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES OF ANY KIND ARISING FROM THE USE OF THIS WEBSITE, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL PUNITIVE AND CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES.
© 2020 Concordia Technology Solutions. All rights reserved.
[fa icon="chevron-up"]
